{
  "$schema": "./schema.json",
  "title": "Prepositions Quiz",
  "slug": "prepositions",
  "language": "en",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "aboard",
      "answer": "on or into a ship, aircraft, train, or other vehicle",
      "choices": [
        "on or into a ship, aircraft, train, or other vehicle",
        "under something",
        "beside something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "at a higher level or layer than",
        "on the subject of; concerning"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "about",
      "answer": "on the subject of; concerning",
      "choices": [
        "on the subject of; concerning",
        "above something",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "on or into a ship, aircraft, train, or other vehicle",
        "at a lower level or layer than"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "above",
      "answer": "at a higher level or layer than",
      "choices": [
        "at a higher level or layer than",
        "below something",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the time following an event",
        "in opposition to"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "across",
      "answer": "from one side to the other of something",
      "choices": [
        "from one side to the other of something",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "at a higher level or layer than",
        "surrounded by; in the middle of"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "after",
      "answer": "in the time following an event",
      "choices": [
        "in the time following an event",
        "before something",
        "beside something",
        "under something",
        "in opposition to",
        "moving in a constant direction on a path"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "against",
      "answer": "in opposition to",
      "choices": [
        "in opposition to",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "surrounded by; in the middle of",
        "at the side of; next to"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "along",
      "answer": "moving in a constant direction on a path",
      "choices": [
        "moving in a constant direction on a path",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "beside something",
        "surrounded by; in the company of",
        "located or situated on every side"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "amid",
      "answer": "surrounded by; in the middle of",
      "choices": [
        "surrounded by; in the middle of",
        "on the surface of something",
        "beside something",
        "under something",
        "used to indicate by comparison the way that something happens",
        "used to indicate a specific location or time"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "among",
      "answer": "surrounded by; in the company of",
      "choices": [
        "surrounded by; in the company of",
        "beside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "earlier than a particular time or event",
        "at the back of something"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "around",
      "answer": "located or situated on every side",
      "choices": [
        "located or situated on every side",
        "inside something",
        "under something",
        "beside something",
        "used to indicate by comparison the way that something happens",
        "used to indicate a specific location or time"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "as",
      "answer": "used to indicate by comparison the way that something happens",
      "choices": [
        "used to indicate by comparison the way that something happens",
        "on the surface of something",
        "beside something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "used to indicate a specific location or time",
        "earlier than a particular time or event"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "at",
      "answer": "used to indicate a specific location or time",
      "choices": [
        "used to indicate a specific location or time",
        "inside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "beside something",
        "earlier than a particular time or event",
        "at the back of something"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "before",
      "answer": "earlier than a particular time or event",
      "choices": [
        "earlier than a particular time or event",
        "after something",
        "beside something",
        "under something",
        "at the back of something",
        "at a lower level or layer than"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "behind",
      "answer": "at the back of something",
      "choices": [
        "at the back of something",
        "inside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "below something",
        "at a higher level or layer than",
        "directly under something"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "below",
      "answer": "at a lower level or layer than",
      "choices": [
        "at a lower level or layer than",
        "above something",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "directly under something",
        "at the side of; next to"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "beneath",
      "answer": "directly under something",
      "choices": [
        "directly under something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "beside something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "at the side of; next to",
        "in the space separating two things"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "beside",
      "answer": "at the side of; next to",
      "choices": [
        "at the side of; next to",
        "inside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "below something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "at or to the further side of"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "between",
      "answer": "in the space separating two things",
      "choices": [
        "in the space separating two things",
        "inside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "below something",
        "at or to the further side of",
        "except; other than"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "beyond",
      "answer": "at or to the further side of",
      "choices": [
        "at or to the further side of",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "except; other than",
        "identifying the agent performing an action"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "but",
      "answer": "except; other than",
      "choices": [
        "except; other than",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "identifying the agent performing an action",
        "about; regarding"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "by",
      "answer": "identifying the agent performing an action",
      "choices": [
        "identifying the agent performing an action",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "about; regarding",
        "taking into account"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "concerning",
      "answer": "about; regarding",
      "choices": [
        "about; regarding",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "taking into account",
        "without being affected by"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "considering",
      "answer": "taking into account",
      "choices": [
        "taking into account",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "without being affected by",
        "from a higher to a lower place or position"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "despite",
      "answer": "without being affected by",
      "choices": [
        "without being affected by",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "from a higher to a lower place or position",
        "throughout the duration of"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "down",
      "answer": "from a higher to a lower place or position",
      "choices": [
        "from a higher to a lower place or position",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "throughout the duration of",
        "not including; other than"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "during",
      "answer": "throughout the duration of",
      "choices": [
        "throughout the duration of",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "not including; other than",
        "not including"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "except",
      "answer": "not including; other than",
      "choices": [
        "not including; other than",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "not including",
        "coming after or as a result of"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "excluding",
      "answer": "not including",
      "choices": [
        "not including",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "coming after or as a result of",
        "used to indicate the purpose of something"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "following",
      "answer": "coming after or as a result of",
      "choices": [
        "coming after or as a result of",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "used to indicate the purpose of something",
        "indicating the point in space at which a journey, motion, or action starts"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "for",
      "answer": "used to indicate the purpose of something",
      "choices": [
        "used to indicate the purpose of something",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "indicating the point in space at which a journey, motion, or action starts",
        "inside something"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "from",
      "answer": "indicating the point in space at which a journey, motion, or action starts",
      "choices": [
        "indicating the point in space at which a journey, motion, or action starts",
        "beside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "in the space separating two things",
        "inside something",
        "within the interior of something"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "in",
      "answer": "inside something",
      "choices": [
        "inside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "within the interior of something",
        "moving or being moved inside something"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "inside",
      "answer": "within the interior of something",
      "choices": [
        "within the interior of something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "moving or being moved inside something",
        "similar to"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "into",
      "answer": "moving or being moved inside something",
      "choices": [
        "moving or being moved inside something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "similar to",
        "less; reduced by"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "like",
      "answer": "similar to",
      "choices": [
        "similar to",
        "on the surface of something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "less; reduced by",
        "at or to a short distance away"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "minus",
      "answer": "less; reduced by",
      "choices": [
        "less; reduced by",
        "on the surface of something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "at or to a short distance away",
        "expressing the relationship between a part and a whole"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "near",
      "answer": "at or to a short distance away",
      "choices": [
        "at or to a short distance away",
        "on the surface of something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "expressing the relationship between a part and a whole",
        "away from the surface of something"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "of",
      "answer": "expressing the relationship between a part and a whole",
      "choices": [
        "expressing the relationship between a part and a whole",
        "on the surface of something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "away from the surface of something",
        "on the surface of something"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "off",
      "answer": "away from the surface of something",
      "choices": [
        "away from the surface of something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "inside something"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "on",
      "answer": "on the surface of something",
      "choices": [
        "on the surface of something",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "moving to a position on the surface of something",
        "in a position facing something else"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "onto",
      "answer": "moving to a position on the surface of something",
      "choices": [
        "moving to a position on the surface of something",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "in a position facing something else",
        "situated or moving beyond the confines of something"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "opposite",
      "answer": "in a position facing something else",
      "choices": [
        "in a position facing something else",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "situated or moving beyond the confines of something",
        "extending directly upward from"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "outside",
      "answer": "situated or moving beyond the confines of something",
      "choices": [
        "situated or moving beyond the confines of something",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "extending directly upward from",
        "to or on the further side of"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "over",
      "answer": "extending directly upward from",
      "choices": [
        "extending directly upward from",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "to or on the further side of",
        "for each; to each"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "past",
      "answer": "to or on the further side of",
      "choices": [
        "to or on the further side of",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "for each; to each",
        "with the addition of"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "per",
      "answer": "for each; to each",
      "choices": [
        "for each; to each",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "with the addition of",
        "concerning; about"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "plus",
      "answer": "with the addition of",
      "choices": [
        "with the addition of",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "concerning; about",
        "located or situated on every side"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "regarding",
      "answer": "concerning; about",
      "choices": [
        "concerning; about",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "located or situated on every side",
        "except; other than"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "round",
      "answer": "located or situated on every side",
      "choices": [
        "located or situated on every side",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "except; other than",
        "from a past time until now"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "save",
      "answer": "except; other than",
      "choices": [
        "except; other than",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "from a past time until now",
        "used in expressions introducing an exception or contrast"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "since",
      "answer": "from a past time until now",
      "choices": [
        "from a past time until now",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "used in expressions introducing an exception or contrast",
        "moving in one side and out of the other side of"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "than",
      "answer": "used in expressions introducing an exception or contrast",
      "choices": [
        "used in expressions introducing an exception or contrast",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "moving in one side and out of the other side of",
        "expressing motion in the direction of a particular location"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "through",
      "answer": "moving in one side and out of the other side of",
      "choices": [
        "moving in one side and out of the other side of",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "expressing motion in the direction of a particular location",
        "in the direction of"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "to",
      "answer": "expressing motion in the direction of a particular location",
      "choices": [
        "expressing motion in the direction of a particular location",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "in the direction of",
        "in the direction of"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "toward",
      "answer": "in the direction of",
      "choices": [
        "in the direction of",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something",
        "in the direction of",
        "below something"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "towards",
      "answer": "in the direction of",
      "choices": [
        "in the direction of",
        "inside something",
        "below something",
        "at the back of something"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "under",
      "answer": "below something",
      "choices": [
        "below something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "directly beneath something",
        "different from"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "underneath",
      "answer": "directly beneath something",
      "choices": [
        "directly beneath something",
        "on the surface of something",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "different from",
        "up to the point in time or the event mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "unlike",
      "answer": "different from",
      "choices": [
        "different from",
        "on the surface of something",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "up to the point in time or the event mentioned",
        "from a lower to a higher point"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "until",
      "answer": "up to the point in time or the event mentioned",
      "choices": [
        "up to the point in time or the event mentioned",
        "on the surface of something",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "from a lower to a higher point",
        "more formal term for on"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "up",
      "answer": "from a lower to a higher point",
      "choices": [
        "from a lower to a higher point",
        "on the surface of something",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "more formal term for on",
        "against; in contrast to"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "upon",
      "answer": "more formal term for on",
      "choices": [
        "more formal term for on",
        "on the surface of something",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "against; in contrast to",
        "traveling through (a place) en route to a destination"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "versus",
      "answer": "against; in contrast to",
      "choices": [
        "against; in contrast to",
        "on the surface of something",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "traveling through (a place) en route to a destination",
        "accompanied by"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "via",
      "answer": "traveling through (a place) en route to a destination",
      "choices": [
        "traveling through (a place) en route to a destination",
        "on the surface of something",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "accompanied by",
        "inside the limits of"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "with",
      "answer": "accompanied by",
      "choices": [
        "accompanied by",
        "on the surface of something",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "inside the limits of",
        "not having; lacking"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "within",
      "answer": "inside the limits of",
      "choices": [
        "inside the limits of",
        "on the surface of something",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "not having; lacking",
        "on or into a ship, aircraft, train, or other vehicle"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "without",
      "answer": "not having; lacking",
      "choices": [
        "not having; lacking",
        "on the surface of something",
        "inside something",
        "at the back of something",
        "on or into a ship, aircraft, train, or other vehicle",
        "on the subject of; concerning"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
